[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "A new applicant must submit A(DDC) certificate of a defensive driving course that was take within the following time frame.",
    "options": {
      "A": "3 Years",
      "B": "1 Year",
      "C": "2 Years",
      "D": "12 months"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "The Fatigue driving rule establist. How many hour in 24 hours are TLC drivers permitted to transport pasanger ?",
    "options": {
      "A": "8 Hours",
      "B": "10 Hours",
      "C": "12 Hours",
      "D": "15 Hours"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  }
  ,
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "The Vision TRUE-Initiative in NYC Rule out a state speed limit to make a left turn ?",
    "options": {
      "A": "12 MPH",
      "B": "10 MPH",
      "C": "5 MPH",
      "D": "3 MPH"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "In NYC what is the TE Speed limit",
    "options": {
      "A": "25 MPH",
      "B": "30 MPH",
      "C": "35 MPH",
      "D": "15 MPH"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which of the following TLC cars not a (FHB) For-hire BASE",
    "options": {
      "A": "Luxure Limosine NYC Base",
      "B": "Livery car service NYC Base",
      "C": "Black Car NYC Base",
      "D": "Yellow Taxi medallon (Cabs) garage."
    },
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "A new applicant for a TLC driver license must be.",
    "options": {
      "A": "21 year old",
      "B": "19 year old",
      "C": "A new york city resident",
      "D": "Must be able to speak english"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which borough has the three neighborhoods of york",
    "options": {
      "A": "21 year old",
      "B": "19 year old",
      "C": "A new york city resident",
      "D": "Must be able to speak english"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "In how days the TLC driver have to report criminal conviction to the commision.",
    "options": {
      "A": "10 days",
      "B": "15 days",
      "C": "30 days",
      "D": "60 days"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which destination can a TLC driver refuse a passenger",
    "options": {
      "A": "River Nead",
      "B": "Yonker",
      "C": "Park Hill",
      "D": "Lake Success"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  }, {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "A TLC car may not be IDLE for longer than one minute in front of A.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Hospital",
      "B": "Bridge",
      "C": "School",
      "D": "Goverment Building"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },{
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Bellow 59th streat In Manhaman, which way does broadway travel?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Southwest",
      "B": "SouthEast",
      "C": "Northwest",
      "D": "Northeast"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },{
    "id": 12,
    "question": "If a passenger wants to go to newark airport, new jersey from NYC penn station building which one is the nearest watercrossing you are going to take?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Holland Tunnel",
      "B": "Lincon Tunnel",
      "C": "George wasnington bridge",
      "D": "Wasington Bridge"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "If manhattan which street is parallel to west broadway",
    "options": {
      "A": "Canal Streat",
      "B": "Church Streat",
      "C": "Chambers streat",
      "D": "Vesey Streat"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "How many securements for a passenger in a WAV TLC car.",
    "options": {
      "A": "6",
      "B": "2",
      "C": "4",
      "D": "5"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
   {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "When can a TLC driver ask for a tip to a customer",
    "options": {
      "A": "Before the trip start if the driver nelpeol with language.",
      "B": "After the trip ended.",
      "C": "During the  trip if is a night time",
      "D": "Never"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  },{
    "id": 16,
    "question": "When can TLC a driver (FHV) for-hired vehical driver pickup a family member?",
    "options": {
      "A": "When the police permit",
      "B": "After the trip ended.",
      "C": "During the  trip if is a night time",
      "D": "Never"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  }

]